<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PieBuilder</string>
    <string name="about">Here at PieBuilder it is our mission to understand our customers by first asking a series of questions in hopes of gaining valuable insights into their level of risk tolerance, financial
        goals, and expected outcome from their investments. From there, we then give a calculated recommendation on the way they should distribute their capital within the financial markets. This recommendation
        is based on the users answers to the preliminary questions, and may include things such as stocks, bonds, cryptocurrency and real estate.</string>

    <string name="question_age">How old are you?</string>
    <string name="question_income">What is your total annual income?</string>
    <string name="question_net_worth">What is your total net worth (Assets - Liabilities)?</string>
    <string name="question_objectives">What is your main objective for this portfolio?</string>
    <string name="question_time_horizon">What is your time horizon?</string>
    <string name="question_investing_knowledge">How would you describe your investing knowledge?</string>
    <string name="question_volatility">How would you feel if your portfolio\'s value decreased by 10% in a few weeks?</string>
    <string name="question_portfolio_growth_decline">If you were to invest $100000, knowing you could gain or lose money, which of these scenarios are you most comfortable with?</string>

    <string name="low_risk_profile">Your answers indicate that you prefer low risk at the cost of less than average but consistent returns. Given this, we recommend a heavy allocation towards fixed income assets
        such as bonds, GIC\'s, and other fixed income vehicles such as a high interest TFSA</string>
    <string name="low_risk_holdings"><b>30% Cash</b>\n\n
                                    <b>50% ETF\'s:</b>\n\n
                                    Vanguard Canadian Aggregate Bond Index ETF (VAB.TO)\n
                                    iShares Core Conservative Allocation ETF (AOK)\n
                                    Vanguard S&amp;P 500 ETF (VOO)\n
                                    Vanguard Total Stock Market Index Fund ETF Shares (VTI)\n
                                    \n
                                    <b>20% Individual Stocks:</b>\n\n
                                    Canadian National Railway Company (CNR.TO)\n
                                    Home Depot (HD)\n
                                    TELUS Corp (T.TO)\n</string>
    <string name="medium_risk_profile">Your answers indicate that you prefer medium risk to expose yourself to roughly average annual returns. Given this, we recommend a minority allocation to fixed income assets
    such as bonds, GIC\'s, and other fixed income vehicles such as a high interest TFSA. The majority of your allocation should reside in medium to large cap stocks with a consistent history of growth. The remainder
    of your capital should be directed to well diversified index funds in an attempt to further diversify and minimize over-exposure to one sector</string>
    <string name="medium_risk_holdings"><b>20% Cash</b>\n\n
                                        <b>50% ETF\'s:</b>\n\n
                                        Vanguard S&amp;P 500 ETF (VOO)\n
                                        Vanguard Total Stock Market Index Fund ETF Shares (VTI)\n
                                        Invesco QQQ Trust (QQQ)\n
                                        Vanguard FTSE Emerging Markets Index Fund ETF Shares (VWO)\n
                                        \n
                                        <b>30% Individual Stocks</b>\n\n
                                        The Walt Disney Company (DIS)\n
                                        Amazon.com Inc (AMZN)\n
                                        Walmart Inc (WMT)\n</string>
    <string name="high_risk_profile">Your answers indicate that you are comfortable with the volatility accompanied with a portfolio that\'s capable of much higher possible returns. Given this, our recommendation would be
    to first build a high quality foundation of either growth stocks with a large market cap or ETF\'s. This foundation will minimize the volatility but still keep you on track to reach those high potential returns.
    From there we\'d recommend putting a large portion of capital into speculative, high growth stocks in disruptive sectors like electric vehicles, renewable energy, genomics and fintech. You may also want to consider
    starting a position in the crypocurrency space. Finally, we also recommend keeping a bit of cash on the side to buy the dip when it inevitablty comes.</string>
    <string name="high_risk_holdings"><b>10% Cash</b>\n\n
                                      <b>20% Foundational Stocks and ETF\'s\n\n</b>
                                      Vanguard S&amp;P 500 ETF (VOO)\n
                                      Amazon.com Inc (AMZN)\n
                                      Apple Inc. (AAPL)\n
                                      Home Depot (HD)\n
                                      The Walt Disney Company (DIS)\n
                                      \n
                                      <b>50% High Growth Stocks</b>\n\n
                                      Tesla Inc (TSLA)\n
                                      Square Inc (SQ)\n
                                      Upstart Holdings Inc (UPST)\n
                                      CRIPSR Therapeutics AG (CRSP)\n
                                      NIO Limited (NIO)\n
                                      Palantir Technologies Inc(PLTR)\n
                                      \n
                                      <b>20% Cryptocurrecy</b>\n\n
                                      Bitcoin\n
                                      Ethereum\n
                                      Aave\n
                                      Cardano\n</string>
</resources>